hides.at 2017-05-23

# Hides.at

## LEGAL PRIVACY POLICY for  site

We at  site respect the privacy of our visitors and understand that your online safety is above all . 

The Privacy Policy is updated from time to time; therefore we advise you to check it from time to time . 

### 1\. Collected Information 

Data can be colected and processed during the operations of our website . We may perform these actions in the following ways :

1.1. Data regarding your visit(s) to our website and any resourced used are collected. The following is included and not limited to: location data, traffic data, and any other communication information.

1.2. Any forms you filled out on our site allows us to collect data such as registering for information when you complete a purchase.

1.3. If for any reason you communicate with our staff or site we may collect information.

### 2\. Cookie Usage 

We may use cookies to gather information regarding our services. 

2.1. All information collected will not have any indentifying data , no personal details will be shared that could identify you.

### 3\. Our use of Your Information

Information stored or collected ragarding you helps us improve and offer services you need. 

3.1. And existing customer may be contacted regarding products and services related to any item of previous sale you make on our site.

3.2. We may use data or allow third parties to use information that is not related to good or services you may be interesed in. 

3.3. None of the information collected about you will offer identifiable characteristics. Information shared to a third party is statistical only. We will not reveal who you are or any personal information , only mathematical information about our visitors.

### 4\. Personal Data Storage

4.1. Information we are provided will be store on secure servers. Transaction data is encrypted for your safety.

4.2. You should understand data via online transmission is not completely secure . We cannot guarantee full protection and security data, only that we take all posible action to protect information sent to us electronically. Transmission of any data by you is at your own risk.

### 5\. Third Party Links 

Third party links maybe be discovered on our site. These third party links have their own privacy policy , which you agree to when you visit them. We are not responsabile nor do we accept responsability for third party links. Our liability covers us only on our website .

### 6\. Contacting us

Please feel free to contact us with any questions or problems related to our Privacy Policy, also feel free to contact us with any questions related to our website via our contact form .
